* Lifetime available [Buy Premium](https://www.stickypassword.com/buy-premium)

Privacy and Personal Data Protection Policy of Lamantine Software a. s.
=======================================================================

We recognize the need to protect the personal data of all users and visitors to our web pages. We confirm that our actions are in compliance with both the Privacy Act of our home country, the Czech Republic (Act no. 101/200 Sb), as well as European Union 2016/679 General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Data we collect
---------------

We collect and retain only 1) data that is needed to maintain the quality of our products and services at the highest possible level and 2) data that is essential for providing support to users of our products and services.

### When you visit our website and use our services

We may collect details about devices including: your IP address, device identifiers, your operating system, browser type, or other technical details provided by your web browser.  
We may collect anonymous data about your usage (e.g. which features you use) of Sticky Password.

We may use so-called "cookies" to track visitors to our websites. Cookie technology is used to facilitate navigation of the website. Cookies are small pieces of unique information, sent by a website, that are stored on your hard drive and temporarily in your computer's memory by your web browser. This allows the website to recognize you as you move through the website without your having to enter any personal information.

If you do not want this information to be stored on your computer, refer to the “Help” section of your browser for the appropriate settings.This will allow you also to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies as well as offering other options and settings concerning cookies.

We may use 3rd party cookies such as Facebook, Google Analytics, Google AdWords, GoSquared, Sklik, Zendesk.

You may refuse to accept cookies at any time by activating the setting on your browser or device which allows you to refuse cookies. Further information about the procedure to follow in order to disable cookies can be found on your Internet browser provider’s website via your help screen. Please be aware that if cookies are disabled, not all features of our website may operate as intended.

### When you create your StickyAccount

You create your StickyAccount when installing Sticky Password for the first time. You will need to provide us with your email address, and to create your own personal Master Password. Your Master Password is the only way to access your data stored in Sticky Password. Only you know your Master Password, it is never sent to our servers. Keep it in secret and do not share it with others.

### When you make a purchase on our site

We ask only for necessary payment processing information, including, as applicable, your credit card details, email address and country. If you are a business, you may want to provide us with your company details such as company name, VAT ID and address.

### When you submit a crash log or bug report

Sticky Password will generate bug- or crash reports which you have the option to allow to be sent to us. In addition to technical information that will allow us to address the problem, these reports may include your e-mail address (StickyID).  
Certain crash reports might be sent automatically. Such reports are anonymized and cannot be linked to an individual.

### When you contact us for customer support

When you ask our customer support team for assistance we may request your e-mail address (StickyID).

How we use the data we collect
------------------------------

We use the above information for the following purposes:

### Providing the service

The data we collect are important for our service to work including optional cloud synchronization and backup and access to your secure StickyAccount.

### Processing the payment

We can complete orders initiated by you via our web pages and process credit card payments via our e-commerce partners. We never store credit card details. These are securely submitted directly to the e-commerce partner.

### Providing you with important information

We provide you with important information related to your usage of our services like authorization PINs, etc.

### Providing customer support

We use your contact information from the logs and your customer support requests to provide you assistance and fixes.

### Keeping our services secure

We use the information we get from website traffic and about your devices to protect our services against attacks.

### Fulfilling our legal obligations

We store the data about the orders you made as mandated by law.

### Implementing improvements

We use the information we get from you to improve our services.

### Informing you about news and special offers

From time to time, we may send you news about our services, as well as special offers. You can unsubscribe from these emails at any time.

### Marketing

We may use cookies to provide you interest-based ads based on your visit to our website or to track commissions for our affiliate partners.

What are your rights
--------------------

* You have the right to access information collected about you,
* you may request that we delete your personal information from our system,
* you may have the right to ask us to rectify/correct your personal information,
* you have the right to withdraw any consent for processing of your personal information you provided previously.

Send any requests and queries regarding your personal information to our customer support team ([\[email protected\]](https://www.stickypassword.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)).

Please note that we may reject your request to delete your personal information if these are needed for us to provide the service to you and/or to fulfill our legal obligations.

Information you share
---------------------

You may elect to share with others your personal information that is stored in Sticky Password, including your e-mail address (StickyID). We are not responsible for the activities of other users you share your personal information with.

Information we share
--------------------

We do not share personal information with any 3rd parties without your explicit consent with the following exceptions:

### Customer support

We may involve our business partners in the process in order to provide you customer support in your language.

### Developers

Our contract developers might work on fixes based on your crash- or bug report.

### External processing

We may share anonymized usage data with data analysis services (like Google Analytics) to help us improve our services.

### Legal reasons

We share personal information with 3rd parties when such disclosure, access, storage and/or processing of the information is necessary to:

* adhere to applicable laws, regulations, legal processes or enforceable governmental request.
* enforce our End-user license agreement, as well as examination of possible violations.
* address potential security (including fraud) and technical issues.

All 3rd parties with whom we share personal information are contractually bound to uphold the strict security regulations by which we ourselves are bound to safeguard your data.

Personal information security
-----------------------------

We take all reasonable care to ensure that the personal data described in this Policy are available only to those of our employees or contractors for whom access is necessary to perform their work. The personal data that we acquire is stored on servers that are protected against unauthorized access. You may make use of password-protected services on our web pages that are protected by your Master Password. You take full responsibility for your behavior as regards password security and secure access to such protected areas. We cannot take responsibility for unauthorized access to personal data that occurs during data transfers resulting from security failures in systems other than our systems. Such data transfers may take place when data is being delivered outside the infrastructure that is under our exclusive control.

Data stored in our products
---------------------------

All personal information stored in Sticky Password, including passwords are stored in encrypted format („Encrypted Data“) only on your computer or other designated devices. As such these data are not accessible to us. If you decide to activate the synchronization service and/or use the secure sharing feature, the Encrypted Data are sent to our servers or to servers of storage providers selected by us in order to ensure such a service. Neither we nor the storage service provider have access to any of the Encrypted Data. Your data is encrypted on your device(s) before it is sent, and decrypted on your device(s) when you access it. Only you have the key to decrypt the data in the form of your Master Password.

This Privacy Policy version is valid as of 25th May 2018.

By buying a Premium license you help to save endangered manatees around the world.  

© 2001 — 2024 Lamantine Software. Protecting millions of passwords since 2001.

Intel and the Intel logo are trademarks of Intel Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries.
